Inauguration 2009 Sermons and Orations Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Submissions, 2008-2009
  - First Presbyterian Church (Ann Arbor, Michigan)
    - From God's Mouth to Your Ears, 2009-01-18, 1 pamphlet (Box-folder 5/198)
  - Zion Hill Baptist Church (Youngstown, Ohio)
    - To Sing a New Song, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/199)
    - To Sing a New Song, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0236_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Lexington (Lexington, Kentucky)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 5/200)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 2 video recordings: MiniDV; afc2009001_0237_mv01-mv02
  - First Church of Christ, Scientist (Springfield, Illinois)
    - Christian Science Lecture, 2009-01-19, 1 video recording: MiniDV; afc2009001_0238_mv01
  - Horn Lake High School (Horn Lake, Massachusetts)
    - Morning Thoughts, 2008-11-05 (Box-folder 5/201)
  - Greater New Hope Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - Lincoln, King and Obama, 2009-01-18, 5 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0240_sr01-sr05 (Box 12)
  - Chevy Chase Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 5/202)
    - Dear Mr. President- An Open Letter to President Obama, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0241_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Temple Beth David (Rochester, New York)
    - Shelmot President Obama, 2009-01-17, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/203)
  - Concerned Black Citizens Coalition of Clayton County (Riverdale, Georgia)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/204)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/204)
    - Letter, 2009-01-12 (Box-folder 5/204)
    - A Weekend of Celebration and Change,2009-01-18, 1 flyer (Box-folder 5/204)
    - Photographs of event, 2009-01-18, 7 photographic prints: color, 4 x 6 in.; afc2009001_0243_ph01-ph07 (Box-folder 5/204)
  - Antioch Baptist Church (Upper Marlboro, Maryland)
    - Dreams Do Come True, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0244_mv01 (Box 8)
    - Dreams Do Come True, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0244_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Unitarian Church of Barneveld (Barneveld, New York)
    - One More Step: Toward the Dream the Dreamers Dreamed, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/205)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/205)
    - One More Step: Toward the Dream the Dreamers Dreamed, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0245_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Ethical Culture Fieldston School (New York, New York)
    - Letter to Parents, 2009-01-20 (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Sophie Halper, 2009-01-20, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Roma Murphy, 2009-01-20, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Maxine Stern, 2009-01-20, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Lexa Harpel, 2009-01-20, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Ben Their, 2009-01-20, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Aurora Celestin, 2009-01-20, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Julie Cohen, 2009-01-20, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/206)
    - Photographs of event, 2009-01-20, 4 photographs: digital, color, jpg files; afc2009001_0246_ph01-ph04.jpg
    - Inauguration speeches, 2009-01-20, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0246_mv01 (Box 8)
  - New Jerusalem Church (Pretty Prairie, Kansas)
    - Inauguration Sermon, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/207)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/207)
    - Inauguration Sermon, 2009-01-18, 3 sound recording: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0247_sr01-sr03 (Box 12)
  - Good Samaritan Center (Pinellas Park, Florida)
    - Inaugurating the Kin-Dom, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/208)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/208)
    - Inaugurating the Kin-Dom, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0248_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Outreach for Jesus Church and Christian Education Center, Inc. (Hope Mills, North Carolina)
    - Program, 2009-01-23 (Box-folder 6/209)
    - Letters, 2009-01-23, 6 letters (Box-folder 6/209)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-23, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0249_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Milton Seventh-Day Adventist Church (Milton-Freewater, Oregon)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-17, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0250_sr01 (Box 12)
  - St. Stephen United Methodist Church (Arlington, Texas)
    - When God Calls You, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/210)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/210)
    - When God Calls You, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0251_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Door County (Sister Bay, Wisconsin)
    - Flyer and promotional items, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/211)
    - Poems, creative writing, letters and speeches, 2009-01-17, 8 interleaving files (Box-folder 6/211)
    - Order of Service, 2009-01-17 (Box-folder 6/211)
    - Order of Service, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/211)
    - Church service, 2009-01-17, 4 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on 4 CDs; afc2009001_0252_sr01-sr04 (Box 12)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-17, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0252_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Vedanta Society of Kansas City (Kansas City, Missouri)
    - Letter, 2009-01-22 (Box-folder 6/212)
    - Program, 2009-01-18, 1 digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0253_ms02.pdf (Box-folder 6/212)
    - Vivekananda: Prophet of Harmony, 2009-01-18, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/212)
    - Tracing the Heroes' Journey of Swami Vivekananda and Barack Obama, 2009-01-18, 1 speech: digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0253_ms04.pdf (Box-folder 6/212)
    - Speech delivered by Arvind K. Khetia, 2009-01-18, 1 speech (Box-folder 6/212)
    - Symposium: Vivekananda Prophet of Harmony #3005, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0253_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Fifteenth Street Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/213)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0254_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Mount Olive C.M.E Church (Fort Valley, Georgia)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/214)
    - DVD cover, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/214)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0255_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Leftist Marching Band (Portsmouth, New Hampshire)
    - Opening Remarks, 2009-01-20 (Box-folder 6/215)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/215)
    - "Error Bash" liner notes, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/215)
    - Photographs of event, 2009-01-18, 106 photographs: digital, color, jpg files and print copies; afc2009001_0256_ph001-ph106.jpg (Box-folder 6/215)
    - End of an Error, 2009-01-18, 41 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on 4 CDs; afc2009001_0256_sr01-sr41 (Box 12 and 18)
  - St. Andrews Episcopal Church (Fullerton, California)
    - A New President, An Old Destiny, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/216)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/216)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: DVD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0257_mv01 (Box 17)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Evansville (Evansville, Indiana)
    - We Are the Ones: Avoiding Fascism in a Turbulent World, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/217)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/217)
    - We Are the Ones: Avoiding Fascism in a Turbulent World, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0258_sr01 (Box 18)
  - Rev. Jean Smith (Ft. Washington, Maryland)
    - Sermon, 1 sound recording: CD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0259_sr01 (Box 17)
  - Memorial Baptist Church (Hartford, Connecticut)
    - A New Start, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/218)
  - Wallace Memorial Baptist Church (Knoxville, Tennessee)
    - How to Be a Biblical Christian in a Barack Obama World, 2008-11-16, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/219)
    - Program, 2008-11-16 (Box-folder 6/219)
    - Newspaper article (Box-folder 6/219)
    - Sermon, 2008-11-16, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0261_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Congregational Church of Union (Union, Connecticut)
    - Unsolicited Advice, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/220)
    - DVD cover, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 6/220)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0262_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Immanuel United Church of Christ (Sedalia, Missouri)
    - You Will See Greater Things, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/221)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/221)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0263_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Kansas City, Missouri)
    - Tomorrow Has Come! 2009-01-19 (Box-folder 6/222)
  - New Hope Baptist Church (Grand Rapids, Michigan)
    - Church service, 2009-01-25, 11 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0265_sr01-sr11 (Box 18)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0265_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Vedanta Society of St. Louis (St. Louis, Missouri)
    - Letter, 2009-02-26 (Box-folder 6/223)
    - Lecture, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0266_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Metropolitan Community Church of Northern Virginia (Fairfax, Virginia)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/224)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0267_sr01-sr03 (Box 18)
  - Shiloh Baptist Church (Plainfield, New Jersey)
    - When Hope Makes a Difference, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/225)
    - Biography of Rev. Gerald Lamont Thomas, Ph.D., 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/225)
    - Rev. Gerald Lamont Thomas, Ph.D., 2009-01-18, 1 photographic print: color, 2 x 3 in.; afc2009001_0268_ph01 (Box-folder 6/225)
    - When Hope Makes a Difference, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: DVD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0268_mv01 (Box 17)
  - Christ Church (Alexandria, Virginia)
    - Letter, 2009-02-27 (Box-folder 6/226)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/226)
    - Matthew Cowden, Christ Church, Episcopal Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: MiniDV; afc2009001_0269_mv01
  - Calvary United Methodist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - A Time for Peace: Building the Kingdom by Tearing Down Walls, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/227)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/227)
  - First Baptist Church in Needham (Needham, Massachusetts)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/228)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0272_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Trinity Baptist Church of Metro Atlanta (Decatur, Georgia)
    - Thank God for Jesus, 2009-01-24, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/229)
  - St. Thomas Episcopal Church (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Partners In Change: Jesus, Barack, You and Me, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/230)
    - Church Information, 2009-01-25, 1 website print out (Box-folder 6/230)
    - About the Preacher Shahar Caren Weaver, 2009-01-25, 1 biographical sketch (Box-folder 6/230)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0274_sr01 (Box 18)
  - Athens Friends Meeting (Athens, Georgia)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0275_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Highland Presbyterian Church (Louisville, Kentucky)
    - Wise and Timely, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 6/231)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 6/231)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0276_sr01 (Box 18)
  - St. Peter AME Church (Fort Valley, Georgia)
    - Change is Gonna Come, Change We Can Believe In, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0277_ms01.doc (Box-folder 7/232)
    - I Believe I Will Preach, 2009-01-18, 1 speech: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0277_ms02.doc (Box-folder 7/232)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0277_sr01 (Box 18)
  - Arlington Street Church (Boston, Massachusetts)
    - Call to Worship, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/233)
    - Concerning the Yucca, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/233)
    - Ushering in the Kingdom of Greatness, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/233)
    - Benediction, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/233)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/233)
  - Bethel Christian Fellowship (Westlake Village, California)
    - Standing at the Crossroads of Uncharted Territory, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: CD [damaged]; afc2009001_0279_sr01 (Box 17)
    - Leaving and Entering, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: CD [damaged]; afc2009001_0279_sr02 (Box 17)
  - Metropolitan Seventh-Day Adventist Church (Hyattsville, Maryland)
    - Program, 2009-01-17 (Box-folder 7/234)
    - Program, 2009-01-24 (Box-folder 7/234)
    - Lasting Change, 2009-01-24, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0280_mv01 (Box 9)
    - The Challenge of Change, 2009-01-17, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0280_mv02 (Box 9)
  - Zion Progress Baptist Church (Detroit, Michigan)
    - It's a Great Day, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/235)
    - It's a Great Day, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0281_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Epworth United Methodist Church (Berkeley, California)
    - Infrequent Visions, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/236)
    - Infrequent Visions, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0282_sr01
  - First Atheist Church of True Science (Sacramento, California)
    - DVD cover, 2009-01-26 (Box-folder 7/237)
    - Sermon for Obama Inaugural, 2009-01-26, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0283_mv01 (Box 9)
  - St. James AME Zion Church (Cincinnati, Ohio)
    - The 2009 Inauguration of Barack Obama as America's First African-American President, 1 poem (Box-folder 7/238)
    - Speech (Box-folder 7/238)
  - Savage Memorial Presbyterian Church (Portland, Oregon)
    - A New Birth of Freedom, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/239)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/239)
    - A New Birth of Freedom, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0285_sr01
  - Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Harford County (Churchville, Maryland)
    - With Faith and Fortitude, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/240)
  - Lincoln Street United Methodist Church (Portland, Oregon)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/241)
  - First Congregational Church of Christ (Vancouver, Washington)
    - New Beginnings, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon
  - Isle of Patmos Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - Letter, 2009-03-02 (Box-folder 7/243)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 11 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on 2 CDs; afc2009001_0289_sr01-sr11 (Box 18)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0290_mv01 (Box 9)
  - St. Andrews Church, Presbyterian Church of East Africa (Nairobi, Kenya)
    - Reflections on the Inauguration of Barack Obama, 2009-01-20, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/244)
    - Obama thanksgiving prayer, 2009-01-20 (Box-folder 7/244)
    - Letter to U. S. Embassy, 2009-02-02 (Box-folder 7/244)
    - Program, 2009-01-20 (Box-folder 7/244)
    - Newspaper articles (Box-folder 7/244)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-20, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0291_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Greater Imani Church and Christian Center (Memphis, Tennessee)
    - A Dream Fulfilled, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/245)
    - DVD cover, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 7/245)
    - A Dream Fulfilled, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0292_mv01 (Box 9)
  - United Christian Parish (Reston, Virginia)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0293_mv01 (Box 9)
  - First Unitarian Church of Salt Lake City (Salt Lake City, Utah)
    - Has the Dream Become Fulfilled, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/246)
  - Washington National Cathedral (Washington, D.C.)
    - A New Community, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/247)
    - A New Community, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0295_sr01 (Box 18)
  - Holy Faith Church (Saline, Michigan)
    - Glimpses of the Kingdom, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0296_ms01.doc (Box-folder 7/248)
    - Glimpses of the Kingdom,2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0296_sr01 (Box 18)
  - United Methodist Church of Santa Cruz (Santa Cruz, California)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0297_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Wakefield Lynnfield United Methodist Church (Wakefield, Massachusetts)
    - Wakefield Celebration Comments, 2009-01-18, afc2009001_0298_ms01 (Box-folder 7/249)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0298_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Wakefield (Wakefield, Massachusetts)
    - Reflections on Martin Luther King Jr. and Inauguration, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/250)
    - Reflections on Martin Luther King Jr. and Inauguration, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0299_mv01 (Box 9)
  - Friendship Central Community Church (Chattanooga, Tennessee)
    - Great Expectations, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 7/251)
    - Great Expectations, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0300_sr01 (Box 18)
  - Interdenominational Ministerial Coalition (Louisville, Kentucky)
    - Now is the Time, 2009-01-1, 1 program (Box-folder 7/252)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-1, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0301_mv01 (Box 9)
  - River47 Evangelical Covenant Church (Orange, California)
    - Hope, 2009-01-18, 1 slide show: digital ppt file and printed copy; afc2009001_0302_ms01.ppt (Box-folder 7/253)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0302_sr01 (Box 18)
  - National Sorority of Phi Delta Kappa, Inc. Alpha Xi Chapter (Cleveland, Ohio)
    - Statement of Celebration, 2009-01-24 (Box-folder 7/254)
    - Philosophy Statement and Roster (Box-folder 7/254)
    - Letter, 2009-06-11 (Box-folder 7/254)
  - Travellers Rest Missionary Baptist Church (Morrow, Georgia)
    - Letter, 2009-07-15 (Box-folder 7/255)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 2 video recordings: digital file submitted on 2 DVDs; afc2009001_0304_mv01-mv02 (Box 9)
  - Refuge and Strength Full Gospel Assembly (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Sermon, 2009-02-01, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0305_sr01 (Box 18)
Index of Organizations
The 360 Second Word afc2009001_0128
Abyssinia Baptist Church (Savannah, Ga.) afc2009001_0014
Adath Israel Congregation (Lawrenceville, N.J.) afc2009001_0158
Agudas Achim Congregation (Alexandria, Va.) afc2009001_0016
Ahavath Achim Synagogue (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0105
All Dulles Area Muslim Society (Sterling, Va.) afc2009001_0197
All Saint's Episcopal Church (Salt Lake City, Utah) afc2009001_0050
All Souls Unitarian Universalist Congregation (New London, Conn.) afc2009001_0022
Allen Avenue Unitarian Universalist Church (Portland, Me.) afc2009001_0169
Alpharetta Presbyterian Church (Alpharetta, Ga.) afc2009001_0160
American Atheists afc2009001_0180
Antioch Baptist Church (Upper Marlboro, Md.) afc2009001_0244
Antioch Baptist Church North (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0161
Antioch Missionary Baptist Church (San Antonio, Tex.) afc2009001_0134
Apostolic Faith Church of God of Washington, D.C. afc2009001_0192
Arlington Church of the Brethren (Arlington, Va.) afc2009001_0130
Arlington Street Church (Boston, Mass.) afc2009001_0278
Athens Friends Meeting (Society of Friends: Athens, Ga.) afc2009001_0275
Beth David Reform Congregation (Philadelphia, Pa.) afc2009001_0066
Beth Israel Synagogue (Latrobe, Pa.) afc2009001_0058
Beth Shalom Congregation (Columbia, Md.) afc2009001_0172
Bethel African Methodist Episcopal Church (Dallas, Tex.) afc2009001_0124
Bethel Christian Fellowship (Westlake Village, Calif.) afc2009001_0279
Bethlehem Baptist Church (Edgefield, S.C.) afc2009001_0199
Beulah Baptist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0029
Boston Jewish Spirit (Boston, Mass.) afc2009001_0195
Bow Mills United Methodist Church (Bow, N.H.) afc2009001_0037
Broadway Baptist Church (Fort Worth, Tex.) afc2009001_0164
Brown-Hutcherson Ministries (Grand Rapids, Mich.) afc2009001_0081
Butler Street Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0221
Calvary United Methodist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0271
Campbell Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Church (Virginia Beach, Va.) afc2009001_0046
Centenary United Methodist Church (Winston-Salem, N.C.) afc2009001_0204
Center in the Park (Philadelphia, Pa.) afc2009001_0217
Central Presbyterian Church (Louisville, Ky.) afc2009001_0232
Central Wesleyan Church (Elwood, Ind.) afc2009001_0165
Channing Memorial Church (Ellicott City, Md.) afc2009001_0033
Chevy Chase Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0241
Christ Church, Alexandria afc2009001_0269
Christ Community Church (Plumsteadville, Pa.) afc2009001_0007
Christ Episcopal Church (East Orange, N.J.) afc2009001_0038
Christ Lutheran Church (Dallas, Tex.) afc2009001_0106
Christ Lutheran Church (Germantown, Md.) afc2009001_0155
Church of Saint Ann (Lawrenceville, N.J.) afc2009001_0234
Clarendon Presbyterian Church (Clarendon, Va.) afc2009001_0004
College Street Congregational Church (Burlington, Vt.) afc2009001_0146
Colonial Hills Community of Christ (Blue Springs, Mo.) afc2009001_0129
Columbia Falls United Methodist Church (Columbia Falls, Mont.) afc2009001_0049
Come As You Are Community Church (Fort Wayne, Ind.) afc2009001_0119
Community Church of the Pelhams, United Church of Christ (Pelham, N.Y.) afc2009001_0077
Community Renewal Society (Chicago, Ill.) afc2009001_0132
Community Synagogue (Port Washington, N.Y.) afc2009001_0083
Concerned Black Citizens Coalition of Clayton County (Ga.) afc2009001_0243
Concerned Black Clergy of Metropolitan Atlanta, Inc. afc2009001_0109
Congregation Beth El (South Orange, N.J.) afc2009001_0171
Congregation Beth Israel (Portland, Or.) afc2009001_0120
Congregation B'nai Israel (Boca Raton, Fla.) afc2009001_0088
Congregation Beth Shalom (Napa, Calif.) afc2009001_0003
Congregational Church (Union, Conn.) afc2009001_0262
Congregational Church in Deerfield (Deerfield, Ill.) afc2009001_0142
Congregational Church of South Hempstead, United Church of Christ (South Hempstead, N.Y.) afc2009001_0154
Coptic Church. Diocese of the Southern United States afc2009001_0113
Culmore United Methodist Church (Falls Church, Virginia) afc2009001_0215
Creative Arts Center for Spiritual Living (Los Angeles, Calif.) afc2009001_0091
Dallas Christian College afc2009001_0013
Dennis Union Church (Dennis, Mass.) afc2009001_0131
Dublin Community Church (Dublin, N.H.) afc2009001_0220
Durga Temple (Fairfax Station, Va.) afc2009001_0017
East Friendship Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0150
East Shore Unitarian Church (Bellevue, Wash.) afc2009001_0133
Ebenezer Baptist Church (Atlanta, Ga.) afc2009001_0290
Emanuel Lutheran Church (West Warwick, Conn.) afc2009001_0093
Emmanuel Bible Church (Frederick, Md.) afc2009001_0011
Emmanuel Church in the City of Boston afc2009001_0193
Episcopal Church of the Holy Advent (Clinton, Conn.) afc2009001_0227
Epworth United Methodist Church (Berkeley, Calif.) afc2009001_0282
Ethical Culture Fieldston School afc2009001_0246
Faith Presbyterian Church Reformed (Mesquite, Tex.) afc2009001_0108
Fifteenth Street Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.) afc2009001_0254
First Atheist Church of True Science (Sacramento, Calif.) afc2009001_0283
First Baptist Church (Block Island, R.I.) afc2009001_0064